Guide to the Institute for Health Policy Studies - AIDS Resource Program Records
UCSF Library & CKM
- Subject Files, 1979-1989; Series 5; 5 cartons 1 box 12 folders
  The only real condensing of folders was done with the Conferences section of this series. Originally individual folders had been created for each of these conferences even though a large number of the folders contained only a one or two pieces of paper. These folders were combined to create the date runs found in the finding guide. Note: Like most of the other folders in this collection much of the materials in the folders were arranged reverse chronologically and some randomly within the file. A few of the conferences covered are 1988: Caring for the AIDS Patient (SF), Skills Building Conference (New Orleans) - mentioned in the Nancy Stoller and other Collections; 2nd Annual International Lesbian and Gay Health Conference & AIDS Forum (Boston) - includes the Summer 1988 issue of Sexual Health Reports; AIDS & Mental Health: Beyond the Basics (Berkeley); American Hospitals & Human Values (Tampa); Humane & Dignified Death (SF) - sponsored by the National Hemlock Society, and the California Association of AIDS Agencies Annual Conference (Sacramento) - which Pat Franks attended. 1987: Homosexuality Beyond Disease (Amsterdam); Ethical Issues of Rationing Healthcare (Chicago); AIDS: Fact Versus Fiction (SF); AIDS Business Update (NYC); Media Coverage of AIDS Seminar (DC) - Franks, Curran, etc involved; Life, Death & the Challenge of AIDS (St. Paul) - a Residential Workshop for People with AIDS; AIDS/ARC Update '87 (SF) - draft program, planning committee included Angie Lewis and Barry Day of UCSF;, Conference on AIDS & IV Drug Use (DC) - put on by the Red Cross; AIDS is Everybody's Business (SF) - Union sponsored workshops; AIDS and Ethnic Minorities (SF); and Talks on Natural Therapies for Chronic Viral Diseases (SF).
  Of special interest are the URSA Institute files at the end of the series, which include the AIDS Community Education Effectiveness Study Grant application, as well as correspondence and handwritten notes. AIDS or "AIDS and" subjects take up the equivalent of a full carton. The Annenberg Teleconference folder includes both slides and an audio cassette tape. One of the folders under "Risk Groups - Women" contains the complete Women & AIDS Clinical Resource Guide prepared by the SF AIDS Coalition while, "Risk Groups - Lesbians" contains a clipping and a single pamphlet. Under "Immunity" is a book Mind and Immunity: Behavioral Immunology an annotated bibliography from 1983. Cost of AIDS Care is one of the larger groups of folders. The Funding/Foundation files also contain a wide range of materials including clippings, reports, correspondence, and information on a conference on AIDS funding (in which Philip R. Lee was a participant/organizer). The Healthcare Professionals folders deal with both protecting the professional from the patient and the patient from the professional.
  - AIDS (Box:folder 7:31-38, 8:1-38)
    - AIDS and Adolescents (Box:folder 7:31-32)
      - Clippings, 1987-1988 (Box:folder 7:31)
      - AIDS Education Project: A Curriculum for Teens - Final Report, 1987 (Box:folder 7:32)
    - AIDS and Arts, 1989 (Box:folder 7:33)
    - Basic Reference Articles/Clippings, 1983-1988 (Box:folder 7:34-36)
    - Clinical Definition, 1985; 1987 (Box:folder 7:37)
    - Data Gathering Form, 1987-1988 (Box:folder 7:38)
    - Education (Box:folder 8:1-4)
      - Analysis, 1988 (Box:folder 8:1)
      - Policy, 1988 (Box:folder 8:2)
      - Events/Updates (Box:folder 8:3-4)
        - Clippings, 1988; n.d. (Box:folder 8:3)
        - San Francisco AIDS Foundation Monthly Listings, 1986-1988 (Box:folder 8:4)
    - AIDS and Kaposi's Sarcoma, 1982-1988 (Box:folder 8:5)
    - AIDS and Malignancies, 1983-1988 (Box:folder 8:6)
    - AIDS and Neurological Manifestation, 1985-1988 (Box:folder 8:7)
    - AIDS and Opportunistic Infections, 1983-1988 (Box:folder 8:8)
    - AIDS and Pediatrics, 1984-1988 (Box:folder 8:9)
    - AIDS and "Plagues" of the Past, 1985-1988 (Box:folder 8:10)
    - AIDS and Pneumocystis Carinii Pneumonia, 1984; 1988 (Box:folder 8:11)
    - Reading Material, 1986-1989 (Box:folder 8:12)
    - Research (Box:folder 8:13-22)
      - Organizations, 1984-1988 (Box:folder 8:13)
      - Researchers, 1984-1988 (Box:folder 8:14)
      - Funding Sources, 1983-1988 (Box:folder 8:15)
      - University of California, San Francisco, 1988 (Box:folder 8:16)
      - Center for AIDS Prevention Studies - CAPS (formerly SAMHA) Bibliographies, 1988-1989 (Box:folder 8:17)
    - Substance Abuse and Mental Health in AIDS (SAMHA) Center (Box:folder 8:18-22)
      - Correspondence, 1987 (Box:folder 8:18)
      - National Institute on Drug Abuse, 1982-1987 (Box:folder 8:19)
      - Other Federal Programs, 1987; n.d. (Box:folder 8:20)
      - National Institute on Mental Health, 1987 (Box:folder 8:21)
      - AIDS Clinical Research Center, 1985; 1988 (Box:folder 8:22)
    - Serology Testing, 1985; 1988 (Box:folder 8:23)
    - Therapies (Box:folder 8:24-33)
      - Alternative Therapies, 1984-1988 (Box:folder 8:24-25)
      - Drug Therapies (Box:folder 8:26-30)
        - Correspondence, 1983-1984; RESTRICTED (Box:folder 15:6)
        - Clippings, 1985-1987 (Box:folder 8:26)
        - Correspondence, Articles and Directory of Clinical Trials, 1985-1986 (Box:folder 8:27)
        - Clinical Trials - mostly clippings and articles, 1987-1988 (Box:folder 8:28)
        - AZT, 1985-1988 (Box:folder 8:29)
        - AZT Funding, 1987-1988 (Box:folder 8:30)
      - Drug Development and Marketing, 1986-1988 (Box:folder 8:31)
      - Fraud/Quackery, 1987-1988 (Box:folder 8:32)
      - General, 1984-1987 (Box:folder 8:33)
    - Treatment [Alternative], 1982-1987 (Box:folder 8:34-35)
    - Vaccine (Box:folder 8:36-38)
      - Production, 1988 (Box:folder 8:36)
      - Research, 1984-1988 (Box:folder 8:37)
      - Testing, 1986-1988 (Box:folder 8:38)
  - American Foundation for AIDS Research (AMFAR), 1986-1988 (Box:folder 8:39)
  - American Hospital Association (AHA), 1983; 1988 (Box:folder 8:40)
  - American Medical Association (AMA) - includes 1987 Policy Statement, 1987-1988 (Box:folder 8:41)
  - American Public Health Association (APHA), 1988 (Box:folder 8:42)
  - Annenberg Center for Health Sciences (Box:folder 8:43-44)
    - Publicity/Background Information, 1984-1987 (Box:folder 8:43)
    - Teleconference - Diagnosis and Pharmacotherapy of Depression in Cancer Patients - includes Audio Cassette and Slides, 1987 (Box:folder 8:44)
  - AIDS-related Complex/AIDS-related Conditions (ARC), 1985-1987 (Box:folder 9:1)
  - Association of American Medical Colleges (AAMC), 1988 (Box:folder 9:2)
  - Association of State and Territorial Health Officials, 1986; 1988 (Box:folder 9:3)
  - Bathhouses, Gay, 1984-1988 (Box:folder 9:4)
  - Blood Supply (Box:folder 9:5-9)
    - American Red Cross, 1983-1988 (Box:folder 9:5)
    - Blood Products, 1984-1988 (Box:folder 9:6)
    - Irwin Memorial Blood Bank, 1983-1988 (Box:folder 9:7)
    - Other Community Blood Banks, 1983-1988 (Box:folder 9:8)
    - Private - includes handwritten notes, 1986-1988 (Box:folder 9:9)
  - Censorship and AIDS Educational Materials, 1987 (Box:folder 9:10)
  - Columbia University - Center for Population and Family Health (CPFH), 1987 (Box:folder 9:11)
  - Community College, S.F. District - AIDS Info Packet, 1988-1989 (Box:folder 9:12)
  - Communication Technologies - Report on 4th Probability Sample, 1987 (Box:folder 9:13)
  - Conferences (Box:folder 9:14-35)
    - International (Box:folder 9:14-19)
      - 6th International Conference on AIDS - San Francisco, CA, 1990 (Box:folder 9:14)
      - 4th International Conference on AIDS - Stockholm, Sweden, 1988 (Box:folder 9:15)
      - 3rd International Conference on AIDS - Washington, D.C., 1987 (Box:folder 9:16-17)
      - [2nd ] International Conference on AIDS - Paris, France, 1986 (Box:folder 9:18)
      - [1st] International Conference on AIDS (CDC) - Atlanta, GA, 1985 (Box:folder 9:19)
    - 1988 (Box:folder 9:20-22)
      - July - August (Box:folder 9:20)
      - April - June (Box:folder 9:21)
      - January - March (Box:folder 9:22)
    - 1987 (Box:folder 9:23-24)
      - August - December (Box:folder 9:23)
      - January - July (Box:folder 9:24)
    - 1986 (Box:folder 9:25-32)
      - April - December (Box:folder 9:25)
      - AIDS/ARC Update '86 - UCSF, July 25-26, 1986 (Box:folder 9:26)
      - AIDS & the Medical Humanities - UCSF, April 10-11, 1986 (Box:folder 9:27)
      - AIDS Research, Health Care and Public Health Strategies - SF, April 8, 1986 (Box:folder 9:28)
      - AIDS in the Drug Abuse Community & Heterosexual Transmission - Newark, NJ, March 31- April, 1986 (Box:folder 9:29)
      - AIDS Hope Help: National Episcopal Church Conference on AIDS Crisis - SF, March 4-7, 1986 (Box:folder 9:30)
      - AIDS: A Community Response, Information & Options for Grantmakers - SF, January 30, 1986 (Box:folder 9:31)
      - AIDS Public Policy Dimensions - New York City, January 16-17, 1986 (Box:folder 9:32)
    - 1985 (Box:folder 9:33)
      - IV Drug Use and AIDS - UCSF [Speaker's notes], November 15, 1985 (Box:folder 9:33)
    - 1984 (Box:folder 9:34-35)
      - Psychosocial Aspects of AIDS, Glen Cove, NY [CV's], December 7-9, 1984 (Box:folder 9:34)
      - The AIDS Epidemic: Development of Intervention Strategies - San Francisco, May 4-5, 1984 (Box:folder 9:35)
  - Confidentiality (Box:folder 9:36-38)
    - HIV Antibody Testing/Test Results, 1983-1988 (Box:folder 9:36)
    - Contact Tracing/ Medical History, 1987-1988 (Box:folder 9:37)
    - Research, 1984-1985 (Box:folder 9:38)
  - Corporate/Business Response to AIDS (Box:folder 9:39-41)
    - AIDS: Corporate America Responds, Allstate Insurance, 1988 (Box:folder 9:39)
    - Employee Policies and Programs, 1987-1988 (Box:folder 9:40)
    - New Products and Services, 1986-1988 (Box:folder 9:41)
  - Cost of Care - Literature Reviews, 1987-1988 (Box:folder 9:42)
  - Cost of AIDS Care (Box:folder 9:43-50, 10:1-16)
    - AIDS Care, 1985-1988 (Box:folder 9:43)
    - AIDS Cost of Care Study (Box:folder 9:44-46)
      - Interim Reports to California Department of Health Services (Box:folder 9:44-45)
        - December 1986 - June 1987 (Box:folder 9:44)
        - February 1988 (Box:folder 9:45)
      - Preliminary Final Report, July 30, 1988 (Box:folder 9:46)
    - AIDS Cost of Care "Reader" [includes P.R. Lee testimony to Presidential Commission], 1985-1988 (Box:folder 9:47)
    - AIDS ALERT - Special Issues v. 2:11-12, November-December 1987 (Box:folder 9:48)
    - Economic Impact, 1985-1988 (Box:folder 9:49)
    - Estimating The Direct and Indirect Economic Costs of AIDS - Scitovsky, Rice, Showstack & Lee, 1986-1987 (Box:folder 9:50)
    - Financing Care, Democratic Study Group, US House of Representatives Special Report, 1987-1988 (Box:folder 10:1)
    - The Costs of Treating AIDS Under Medicaid: 1986-1991 - Rand Institute, 1987 (Box:folder 10:2)
    - Boston University Study (Mary C. Reardon), 1986 (Box:folder 10:3)
    - AIDS Inpatient Care in the West Bay, 1988? (Box:folder 10:4)
    - St. Luke's/Roosevelt (NYC) Study, 1985 (Box:folder 10:5)
    - Boston Department of Health/Boston University Study (Seage et al. - includes draft), 1986 (Box:folder 10:6)
    - Blue Cross Study - Medical Costs of AIDS in California - preliminary draft, 1986 (Box:folder 10:7)
    - Harlem - NYC [HIV infected Children], 1988 (Box:folder 10:8)
    - Harvard University Study [2 Progress reports], 1985 (Box:folder 10:9)
    - University of Southern California Proposal for AIDS Cost of Care Study (CDPH), 1986 (Box:folder 10:10)
    - University wide Task Force, Prospective Costs Study, UC San Francisco, 1985-1987 (Box:folder 10:11)
    - General, 1985-1988 (Box:folder 10:12)
    - San Francisco General Hospital, 1984-1986 (Box:folder 10:13)
    - Institute of Medicine Paper - "Confronting AIDS" - cost of care section, n.d. (Box:folder 10:14)
    - Office of Technology Assessment, US Congress - "The Costs of AIDS: Review of the Estimates", 1987 (Box:folder 10:15)
    - Office of Technology Assessment - The Impact of AIDS on the Kaiser Permanente Medical Care Program (Northern California Region, 1988 (Box:folder 10:16)
  - Eisenhower Medical Center, 1987 (Box:folder 10:17)
  - Entertainment Industry and AIDS, 1986-1988 (Box:folder 10:18)
  - Epidemiology of AIDS (Box:folder 10:19-21)
    - Europe, 1986-1988 (Box:folder 10:19)
    - Research Studies, 1986-1988 (Box:folder 10:20)
    - Worldwide, 1985-1988 (Box:folder 10:21)
  - Ethical Issues, 1985-1988 (Box:folder 10:22)
  - ETR Associates (Box:folder 10:23-24)
    - Latino Issues, 1986; 1988 (Box:folder 10:23)
    - AIDS Clearinghouse & Network Publications, 1988 (Box:folder 10:24)
  - Family Planning - Title X AIDS Protocols, 1987 (Box:folder 10:25)
  - Fashion Industry, 1986-1987 (Box:folder 10:26)
  - Foundations, Role of (Box:folder 10:27-36)
    - Council on Foundations, 1986 (Box:folder 10:27)
    - General Information [includes Correspondence], 1985-1988 (Box:folder 10:28)
    - Northern California Grantmakers Conference, 1985-1986; 1988 (Box:folder 10:29)
    - NY Regional Association of Grantmakers, 1987 (Box:folder 10:30)
    - S. H. Cowell Foundation - [2 folders], 1987 (Box:folder 10:31-32)
    - Henry J. Kaiser Family Foundation, 1985 (Box:folder 10:33)
    - William Penn Foundation, 1985 (Box:folder 10:34)
    - Pew Memorial Trusts, 1985; 1987 (Box:folder 10:35)
    - Robert Wood Johnson Foundation, 1986-1989 (Box:folder 10:36)
  - Funding - Public Health Funding Directory for the City and County of San Francisco, 1981 (Box:folder 10:37)
  - Gay and Lesbian Adolescent Social Services, Inc. (GLASS) (Box:folder 10:38)
  - Health Care Providers and AIDS (Box:folder 10:39-43)
    - Nurses, 1985; 1987; n.d. (Box:folder 10:39)
    - Social Workers/Therapists, 1987-1988 (Box:folder 10:40)
    - Physicians, 1984-1988 (Box:folder 10:41)
    - Dental Workers, 1985-1988 (Box:folder 10:42)
    - General, 1983-1988 (Box:folder 10:43)
  - Health Maintenance Organizations (Box:folder 11:1-2)
    - General, 1987-1988 (Box:folder 11:1)
    - Kaiser Foundation Health Plan/Kaiser Permanente, 1987-1988 (Box:folder 11:2)
  - Health Planning and Administration, 1982 (Box:folder 11:3)
  - Hemophilia - Northern California Hemophilia Foundation (NCHF), 1987 (Box:folder 11:4)
  - Hispanic Community and AIDS, 1987-1988 (Box:folder 11:5)
  - Home Care (Box:folder 11:6-7)
    - Industry materials, 1986 (Box:folder 11:6)
    - Clippings and Papers, 1987 (Box:folder 11:7)
  - H.O.M. Group, Inc (Innovators in Healthcare, Organization and Management, 1987 (Box:folder 11:8)
  - Homosexuality, 1983-1988 (Box:folder 11:9)
  - Homosexual Rights, 1983-1988 (Box:folder 11:10)
  - Hospice Care, 1986-1988 (Box:folder 11:11)
  - Hospital Associations West Bay Hospital Conference, 1985-1987 (Box:folder 11:12)
  - Hospital Care (Box:folder 11:13-19)
    - Desert Hospital, 1986 (Box:folder 11:13)
    - Inpatient Care, 1985-1988 (Box:folder 11:14)
    - Kaiser Permanente Medical Facilities, 1986-1987 (Box:folder 11:15)
    - National Association of Public Hospitals Survey, 1986 (Box:folder 11:16)
    - Outpatient Care, 1986 (Box:folder 11:17)
    - Private Hospitals - (AIDS Hospital in Houston), 1986-1987 (Box:folder 11:18)
    - Public Hospitals, 1986-1987 (Box:folder 11:19)
  - Housing, 1986-1988 (Box:folder 11:20)
  - Human Immunodeficiency Virus (HIV) (Box:folder 11:21-27)
    - HIV and Other Deficiencies, 1988 (Box:folder 11:21)
    - Genetic Susceptibility, 1987-1988 (Box:folder 11:22)
    - HIV-like Viruses, 1983; 1987-1988 (Box:folder 11:23)
    - Nature, 1984-1988 (Box:folder 11:24)
    - Infection in Parturients, 1985; 1988 (Box:folder 11:25)
    - Other Viral Diseases, 1984-1988 (Box:folder 11:26)
    - Transmission, n.d. (Box:folder 11:27)
  - HIV Antibody Testing (Box:folder 11:28-35)
    - Military, 1986-1988 (Box:folder 11:28)
    - Test Development and Marketing, 1986-1988 (Box:folder 11:29)
    - Blood Banks, 1984-1986 (Box:folder 11:30)
    - General Information on Test, 1984-1988 (Box:folder 11:31)
    - Employment/Testing in the Workplace, 1986-1988 (Box:folder 11:32)
    - Testing in Other Population Groups, 1987-1988 (Box:folder 11:33)
    - Insurance, 1985-1988 (Box:folder 11:34)
    - Antigen Testing, 1986; 1988 (Box:folder 11:35)
  - HIV Disease, 1984; 1987-1988 (Box:folder 11:36)
  - HIV equals AIDS Debate, 1983; 1988 (Box:folder 11:37)
  - Human Rights/Civil Rights (Box:folder 11:38-42)
    - General, 1985-1988 (Box:folder 11:38)
    - Federal Policies, 1986-1988 (Box:folder 11:39)
    - Local Policies, 1985-1988 (Box:folder 11:40)
    - Private Sector Policies, 1985-1987 (Box:folder 11:41)
    - State Policies, 1985-1988 (Box:folder 11:42)
  - Immune System (Box:folder 11:43-44)
    - Clippings, Articles, etc., 1984-1988 (Box:folder 11:43)
    - Book - Mind and Immunity: Behavioral Immunology: An Annotated Bibliography 1976-1982, 1983 (Box:folder 11:44)
  - Infection Control, 1983-1987 (Box:folder 11:45)
  - Information Networks - AIDS Teleforum, n.d. (Box:folder 11:46)
  - Institute for Advanced Study of Human Sexuality, 1985; 1987 (Box:folder 11:47)
  - Institute for International Research, c. 1986 (Box:folder 11:48)
  - Insurance Companies (Box:folder 12:1-4)
    - Coverage Issues, 1985-1988 (Box:folder 12:1)
    - Rates (also includes random notes and cards), 1984-1988 (Box:folder 12:2)
    - Private Health Insurance, 1987-1988; n.d. (Box:folder 12:3)
    - Information File on AIDS and Insurance, 1987-1988 (Box:folder 12:4)
  - Intergovernmental Health Policy Project (Box:folder 12:5-6)
    - 1985-1986 (Box:folder 12:5)
    - 1987-1988 (Box:folder 12:6)
  - International Institute of San Francisco, 1988 (Box:folder 12:7)
  - Intravenous (IV) Drug Use (Box:folder 12:8-9)
    - General, 1987-1989 (Box:folder 12:8)
    - Goldberg Study and related articles/correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box:folder 12:9)
  - John Hopkins University, 1988 (Box:folder 12:10)
  - Legal Issues re: AIDS, 1984-1988 (Box:folder 12:11)
  - Legal Services, 1985-1988 (Box:folder 12:12)
  - Long Term Care, 1985-1988 (Box:folder 12:13)
  - Media Coverage of AIDS and Sex, 1986-1988 (Box:folder 12:14)
  - Mental Health, 1985-1987 (Box:folder 12:15)
  - Military, 1986-1988 (Box:folder 12:16)
  - National AIDS and Gay Advocacy Organizations and Groups (Box:folder 12:17-33)
    - ACT UP, 1988 (Box:folder 12:17)
    - AIDS Action Council/AIDS Action Foundation, 1987-1988 (Box:folder 12:18)
    - Federation of AIDS-Related Organizations, 1984? (Box:folder 12:19)
    - Gay Rights National Lobby, 1983; 1988 (Box:folder 12:20)
    - Mobilization Against AIDS, 1985; 1988 (Box:folder 12:21)
    - Mother Cares, 1987 (Box:folder 12:22)
    - Names Project, 1987-1988 (Box:folder 12:23)
    - National AIDS Network (Box:folder 12:24-26)
      - 1987-1988 (Box:folder 12:24)
      - 1986-1988 (Box:folder 12:25)
      - 1989 (Box:folder 12:26)
    - National Gay and Lesbian Task Force (NGLTF), 1988 (Box:folder 12:27)
    - National Gay Rights Advocacy, 1986-1988 (Box:folder 12:28)
    - National Leadership Coalition on AIDS, 1987? (Box:folder 12:29)
    - National Network of Educators for AIDS Prevention, 1987 (Box:folder 12:30)
    - Parents and Friends of Lesbians and Gays (PFLAG), 1984 (Box:folder 12:31)
    - SAGE, 1986?; 1988 (Box:folder 12:32)
    - Stop AIDS Foundation (Box:folder 12:33)
  - National Academy of Science - Confronting AIDS, 1986 (Box:folder 12:34)
  - National Association of Counties - AIDS Task Force, 1988 (Box:folder 12:35)
  - National Conference of Mayors, 1987 (Box:folder 12:36)
  - National Foundation for Infectious Diseases, 1986 (Box:folder 12:37)
  - Nursing Services, 1984-1988 (Box:folder 12:38)
  - Nutrition, 1981-1988 (Box:folder 12:39)
  - Persons With AIDS - Personal Stories, 1985-1988 (Box:folder 12:40)
  - Prevention and Control (Box:folder 12:41-47)
    - Condoms, 1986-1988 (Box:folder 12:41)
    - Spermacides, 1987 (Box:folder 12:42)
    - Evalution of Effecivness, 1986-1987 (Box:folder 12:43)
    - Program Evaluation in N.J., N.M. and N.C. - research paper, 1988 (Box:folder 12:44)
    - Information and Education (Box:folder 12:45-47)
      - General Public, 1985-1988; 1983-1986 (Box:folder 12:45-46)
      - High-risk Group, 1984-1988 (Box:folder 12:47)
    - Risk Reduction Programs and Services (High Risk Groups), 1986-1988 (Box:folder 12:48)
    - Risk Reduction Practices, 1984-1988; n.d. (Box:folder 12:49)
  - Private Foundations - Funding for AIDS, 1987 (Box:folder 13:1)
  - Prisons, 1986-1988 (Box:folder 13:2)
  - Psychological Issues, 1983-1988 (Box:folder 13:3)
  - Public/Community Reaction, 1983-1988 (Box:folder 13:4)
  - Public Opinion Polls, 1986-1988 (Box:folder 13:5)
  - Public Policy Issues (Box:folder 13:6-9)
    - Women with AIDS/AIDS & Public Policy Journal, 1987-1988; n.d. (Box:folder 13:6)
    - Federal, 1983-1988 (Box:folder 13:7)
    - Local, 1986-1987 (Box:folder 13:8)
    - State, 1985 (Box:folder 13:9)
  - Public Relations/Benefits for AIDS, 1986-1988 (Box:folder 13:10)
  - Religious and Interfaith AIDS Groups, 1984-1988 (Box:folder 13:11)
  - Religious Dominations' Policies on AIDS and Homosexuality, 1986-1988 (Box:folder 13:12)
  - Risk Groups (Box:folder 13:13-30)
    - Asians, 1988 (Box:folder 13:13)
    - Bisexual Men, 1986-1987 (Box:folder 13:14)
    - Blacks, 1986-1988 (Box:folder 13:15)
    - Blood Transfusion Recipients, 1984-1988 (Box:folder 13:16)
    - Children of Persons with AIDS, 1986-1987 (Box:folder 13:17)
    - Haitians, 1983-1987 (Box:folder 13:18)
    - Hemophiliacs, 1983-1988 (Box:folder 13:19)
    - Heterosexuals, 1985-1988 (Box:folder 13:20)
    - Hispanics, 1988 (Box:folder 13:21)
    - Homosexual Men, 1983-1988 (Box:folder 13:22)
    - Intravenous (IV) Drug Users, 1986-1988 (Box:folder 13:23)
    - Lesbians, 1986-1987 (Box:folder 13:24)
    - Minorities, 1985-1988 (Box:folder 13:25)
    - Native Americans, 1987 (Box:folder 13:26)
    - Organ Donation Recipients, 1985-1988 (Box:folder 13:27)
    - Prostitutes, 1985-1988 (Box:folder 13:28)
    - Women (Box:folder 13:29-30)
      - General, 1985-1988 (Box:folder 13:29)
      - Women and AIDS Clinical Resources Guide, 1986 (Box:folder 13:30)
  - Schools and AIDS (Box:folder 13:31-37)
    - Universities and Colleges, 1986-1988 (Box:folder 13:31)
    - High Schools, 1988 (Box:folder 13:32)
    - Elementary Schools and Day Care, 1987 (Box:folder 13:33)
    - Sex Education/Family Life Education, 1987-1988; n.d. (Box:folder 13:34)
    - Polices re: Students/Teachers with AIDS, 1986-1987 (Box:folder 13:35)
    - AIDS Education and Information (Box:folder 13:36-37)
      - Clippings and Articles, 1986-1988 (Box:folder 13:36)
      - Books, pamphlets, other material, 1979; 1983-1988 (Box:folder 13:37)
  - Sexually Transmitted Diseases, 1982-1988 (Box:folder 13:38)
  - Social Impact of AIDS, 1986-1988 (Box:folder 13:39)
  - States (Box:folder 14:1-3)
    - AIDS Expenditures, 1987 (Box:folder 14:1)
    - AIDS Legislation, 1986-1987 (Box:folder 14:2)
    - AIDS Program Activities, 1985 (Box:folder 14:3)
  - Substance Abuse (Box:folder 14:4-8)
    - Alcohol, 1985-1986 (Box:folder 14:4)
    - Intravenous (IV) Drugs, 1985-1988 (Box:folder 14:5)
    - Other Drugs, 1984-1987 (Box:folder 14:6)
    - Policies, 1985; 1987 (Box:folder 14:7)
    - Programs, 1987-1988 (Box:folder 14:8)
  - URSA Institute (Box:folder 14:9-10)
    - AIDS Community Education Effectiveness, 1986-1987 (Box:folder 14:9)
    - AIDS Supportive Services Assessment, 1982-1986 (Box:folder 14:10)
  - Women and AIDS re: Montreal Conference, 1989 (Box:folder 14:11)
  - Workplace (Box:folder 14:12-13, 15:1-3)
    - Articles and Clippings, 1985-1988 (Box:folder 14:12)
    - Events/Correspondence, etc., 1986-1988 (Box:folder 14:13)
    - Publications (Box:folder 15:1-3)